Now that the face is done, we're going to move on to the eyes.
This is the fun part and the hard part.
The first step is eye shadow base.
That's really easy.
You can't mess this up.
You want to take a nice big brush.
I'm not using something so shimmery because I'm using a lot of shimmer on the rest of her face, so I'm using a very matte, kind of nude, neutral, vanilla color.
It's so natural that you don't have to worry about using too much.
You just really want to pile it on.
I'm taking it right to her eye and I'm just putting it all over the whole entire lid.
That's just going to give a really creamy, cream look.
It's going to be like drawing on a white piece of paper when I'm done.
The next color I put on is going to go on so smooth and look beautiful.
This is just a very, very, natural look.
Like I said, natural vanilla color.
I'm going all over her whole entire eye.
I'm just piling it on.
Look up for me.
I'm taking a little bit underneath just to keep it blended and natural.
Whatever I do on top, I normally do a little bit on the bottom just so that it's all blended and smooth looking.
Close again.
If you get a little powder dust underneath, just clean it up with a brush.
Now I'm ready to put the lid color on.